The bravest place to stand is by each other's side.
Stop-Loss is a drama, war film directed by Kimberly Peirce.
A veteran soldier returns from his completed tour of duty in Iraq, only to find his life turned
upside down when he is arbitrarily ordered to return to field duty by the Army.
Brandon King, played by Ryan Phillippe.
Michelle, played by Abbie Cornish.
Tommy Burgess, played by Joseph Gordon-Levitt.
Steve Shriver, played by Channing Tatum.
Senator Orton Worrell, played by Josef Sommer.
Lieutenant Colonel Boot Miller, played by Timothy Olyphant.
Stop-Loss is a 2008 American war drama film directed by Kimberly Peirce and starring Ryan Phillippe, Channing Tatum, Abbie Cornish
and Joseph Gordon-Levitt as young soldiers whose experience in the Iraq War leaves them psychologically shattered.
It was distributed by Paramount Pictures and produced by MTV Films.
The film received mixed reviews, and earned less than half of its
$25 million production budget at the box office.
The title refers to the U.S.
government's controversial stop-loss policy, which allows the government to extend the term of duty
of soldiers who have already served their contracted number of years of service.
The film explores themes of post-traumatic stress disorder (ptsd),
iraq war veteran, u.s. soldier, woman director.
The tone is emotional.